CHAD CLARKE

WEB DEVELOPER / DIGITAL MARKETER

www.chadclarke.io



EDUCATION

GEORGIAN COLLEGE

Interactive Web Design & Development June 2015 - April 2017

FIRE ETC

FireFighting Aug 2013 - Feb 2014

ELMVALE DISTRICT

High School Sept 2006 - April 2010

EXPERIENCE

NAPOLEON

Digital Marketing / Web Developer January 2016 - Current

FREE LANCE

Wordpress Web Design / Development January 2015 - Current

PERSONAL PROFILE

Hey Im Chad, I'm a web developer. I spend my days, practically every day, experimenting with HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript; dabbling with Node JS and angular; .

My gol is to help build to the success of the company while I experience advancement opportunities.

LANGUAGES

English
PHP
Java Script
HTML
J-Query

INTERESTS

Fitness
Marvel Movies
Hockey
Blogging
Music Festivals

CONTACT

705-795-0645 Barrie, Ontario chadclarke15@gmail.com

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Mac OS
Windows
Adobe Suite
MXTR
Wordpress

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Email Marketing
Design
Content
Development
Seo
Marketing

REFERRENCES

Christine Hamlyn Chris 705-790-6123 519-Project Manager, Seni Napoleon Napo

Chris Thompson 519-242-4515 Senior Developer,

Napoleon